### ABDULAZIZ SAUD ALAJALEEN

COMPUTER SCIENCE (IT), SAP TECHNICAL CONSULTANT

E-Mail: abdulaziz.alajaleen@gmail.com Mobile: +966555777849

### SUMMARY

Experienced IT with a proven track record of working in one of the biggest software companies (SAP) and also working in one of the largest conglomerate business groups in the Middle East (Tamimi Group). Expert in SAP, Oracle & SQL DB administration, Security hardening, Web design and application, programming languages and basic project management. Highly professional IT with a bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals (KFUPM).

### **CERTIFICATES & COURSES**

### SAP:

- One month training in Authorization and Auditing for SAP NetWeaver at SAP Singapore in Dec, 2015
- SAP Certified Technology Associate SAP Authorization and Auditing for NetWeaver 7.31 (C\_AUDSEC\_731)
- One month of SAP Basis consultant intensive course at SAP India, Bangalore in Oct, 2012
- SAP Certified Technology Associate System Administration (Oracle DB) with SAP NetWeaver 7.0 EhP2 (C\_TADM51702)
- One month training in Integration of Business Processes in SAP ERP at SAP Corp in Riyadh, Aug 2012
- SAP Certified in Integration of Business Processes in SAP ERP (TERP10)

#### Non SAP:

- Bootstrap course: JavaScript/HTML/CSS course in Sep 2016
- Short course in 'Ethical Hacking and Security' at KFUPM in June 2012
- Obtained CCNA 1 certificate at KFUPM in late 2010
- ASP.NET web design course at DCC in 2007

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Self-directed and able to take initiatives
- Teamwork oriented
- Time management skills
- Innovative and confident

### **EDUCATION**

### Saudi Electronic University (SEU)

Master in Business Administration

(2021- ongoing)

### King Fahd University of Petroleum and Minerals (KFUPM)

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, with a major GPA of 2.96/4

June/2012

## Dammam Community College (DCC), Branch of KFUPM

Associate degree in Computer Applications, with an overall GPA of 3.68/4 (with Honor)

June/2008

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **SAP Basis Consultant**

Tamimi Holding | 2015 - Present

- Involved in multiple SAP projects full cycle installation and implementation
- Involved in multiple SAP projects EHP upgrade and SPS update, Kernel upgrade
- System refresh, client refresh and usual Basis activates
- o BRtools, TMS and SAProuter administration
- System administration and end-users support

#### **Associate Consultant in Business**

SAP Corp | 2012 - 2014

SAP Young Professional Program (YPP)

### **TRAINING**

# Cooperative program from June 2011 to Jan 2012 in National Center for Digital Certification (NCDC) at

Ministry of Communication and Information Technology (MCIT)

### Summer training in IT department in 2008 at

Al-Jeraisy Co